(Leonard:)Mmm, when really
we're just exiting
(Leonard:)an uncomfortable
situation.
(Sheldon:)Kripke, you know, of all
the people-- Barry Kripke.
I'm so... Are you folding
it like a crazy person
(Sheldon:)to get me to
do it for you?!
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)Oh, give me that.
(Sheldon:)Just out of curiosity,
(Sheldon:)if I were to let something go,
(Sheldon:)how would I do that?
(Penny:)I don't know-- just think
about something else.
(Sheldon:)Can I think
about the spiny anteater?
(Amy:)Sure.
(Sheldon:)The spiny anteater...
(Sheldon:)never went behind my back
and worked with Barry Kripke.
(Sheldon:)That didn't help at all.
(Penny:)You know, some people
try visualization.
(Sheldon:)How does that work?
(Howard(on phone):)Okay,
(Penny:)imagine your problems
are a pen.